# **RAJ DHAR**



Phone: +8801623572706, 01726817635

Email: rajdhar880@gmail.com

Address: Patharghata, Bongshal Road, Kotwali,

## **OBJECTIVE**

Over 3 years of experience in retail sales, customer service, and purchasing. Eight months of experience as a Human Resource Supervisor. Strong knowledge and communications skills have led me to a depth understanding and good knowledge of customer service and office administration.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Post: Receptionist (Front Desk Officer) [June 2022 — Present]
Organization: Chittagong Club Limited

Job Responsibilities:

- greeting and welcoming guests, receiving and delivering all incoming and outgoing mail and packages, answering all calls and directing as needed, scheduling meetings, and coordinating office activities.
- Manage the building log of who is entering and exiting the building

Post: Manager [September 2020 — May 2022] Company: Prema Jewellers

Job Responsibilities:

- Handling the daily operations and management of the store.
- To oversee the staffing requirements of the store.
- Prevent theft and handles advertising and promotions of the store

Receptionist & Cash Handling [April 2018 - August 2020]

**Company: Bangladesh Eye Hospital** 

Job Responsibilities:

- Receiving visitors at the front desk by greeting, welcoming, directing, and announcing them appropriately.
- Maintain office security by following safety procedures and controlling access via the reception desk (monitor logbook, issue visitor badges).
- Answer and direct phone calls in a polite and friendly manner.

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)** 

Southern University of Bangladesh

Major: Human Resource Management (HRM)

Result: 2.90 CGPA, Passing year: 2020

## **Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)**

Chittagong Metropolitan Commerce College

Major: Commerce

Result: 2.83 GPA, Passing Year: 2016 Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

J.M. Sen School and College

Major: Commerce

Result: 3.81 GPA, Passing Year: 2014

## **COMPUTER SKILLS**

• Proficient with Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.

• Knowledge of Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- European Open University Professional Certificate for Human Resource Management
- British Council Book Reading Competition Certificate Award 2017
- Create a Project Charter with Google Docs for Coursera Project Network
- Great Learning Certificate for Customer Relationship Management

## LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

English: Proficient (able to speak, write, and read without much difficulty)

Bangla: Fluent (can read, write, and speak without hesitation)

## REFERENCES

## **Bijov Kumar Tarafder**

Senior Lecturer
Dept. of EEE
Chittagong Institute of Engineering
and Technology (CIET)
Affiliated with University of Chittagong Mobile:
+8801925489868

Email: bijoytarafder@gmail.com/

bijoytarafder@ciet.ac.bd

#### **ABM Rashedul Hasan**

Assistant Professor Department of Business Southern University Bangladesh Mobile: +8801837707787 Email: hasan.rashed@gmail.com

I solemnly declare that all the information furnished in this document is free of errors to the best of my knowledge. I hereby declare that all the information contained in this resume is by facts or truths to my knowledge. I take full responsibility for the correctness of the said information.

